{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 18x + 13 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(55))/2, (-9 -  ?(55))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 13\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*2*13))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*2*13))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(220))/4 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(220))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 7x + 8 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-7 + ?(17))/2, (-7 -  ?(17))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 7, c \u003d 8\nx \u003d (-7 + ?(7*7 - 4*1*8))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-7 - ?(7*7 - 4*1*8))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-7 + ?(17))/2 or x \u003d (-7 - ?(17))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 11x + 21 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-11 + ?(37))/2, (-11 -  ?(37))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 21\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(11*11 - 4*1*21))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-11 - ?(11*11 - 4*1*21))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(37))/2 or x \u003d (-11 - ?(37))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 20x + 3 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-10 + ?(94))/2, (-10 -  ?(94))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 3\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*2*3))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*2*3))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(376))/4 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(376))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 15x + 12 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(33))/8, (-15 -  ?(33))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 12\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*4*12))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*4*12))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(33))/8 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(33))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 9x + 5 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(41))/4, (-9 -  ?(41))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 9, c \u003d 5\nx \u003d (-9 + ?(9*9 - 4*2*5))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-9 - ?(9*9 - 4*2*5))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-9 + ?(41))/4 or x \u003d (-9 - ?(41))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 17x + 16 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-17 + ?(161))/4, (-17 -  ?(161))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 16\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(17*17 - 4*2*16))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-17 - ?(17*17 - 4*2*16))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(161))/4 or x \u003d (-17 - ?(161))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 10x + 9 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-5 + ?(7))/2, (-5 -  ?(7))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 9\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(10*10 - 4*2*9))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-10 - ?(10*10 - 4*2*9))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(28))/4 or x \u003d (-10 - ?(28))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 15x + 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(161))/8, (-15 -  ?(161))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 4\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*4*4))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*4*4))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(161))/8 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(161))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 20x + 16 \u003d 0", "answer": "-1, -4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 16\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*4*16))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*4*16))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(144))/8 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(144))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 12x + 30 \u003d 0", "answer": "-6 + ?(6), -6 - ?(6)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 12, c \u003d 30\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(12*12 - 4*1*30))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-12 - ?(12*12 - 4*1*30))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(24))/2 or x \u003d (-12 - ?(24))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n6x^2 + 18x + 11 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(15))/6, (-9 -  ?(15))/6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 6, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 11\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*6*11))/(2*6) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*6*11))/(2*6)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(60))/12 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(60))/12", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 11x + 27 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-11 + ?(13))/2, (-11 -  ?(13))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 27\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(11*11 - 4*1*27))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-11 - ?(11*11 - 4*1*27))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(13))/2 or x \u003d (-11 - ?(13))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 17x + 10 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-17 + ?(209))/4, (-17 -  ?(209))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 10\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(17*17 - 4*2*10))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-17 - ?(17*17 - 4*2*10))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(209))/4 or x \u003d (-17 - ?(209))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n3x^2 + 17x + 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-17 + ?(277))/6, (-17 -  ?(277))/6", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 3, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 1\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(17*17 - 4*3*1))/(2*3) or x \u003d (-17 - ?(17*17 - 4*3*1))/(2*3)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(277))/6 or x \u003d (-17 - ?(277))/6", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n3x^2 + 20x + 22 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-10 + ?(34))/3, (-10 -  ?(34))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 3, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 22\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*3*22))/(2*3) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*3*22))/(2*3)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(136))/6 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(136))/6", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 9x + 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(73))/4, (-9 -  ?(73))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 9, c \u003d 1\nx \u003d (-9 + ?(9*9 - 4*2*1))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-9 - ?(9*9 - 4*2*1))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-9 + ?(73))/4 or x \u003d (-9 - ?(73))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n3x^2 + 18x + 19 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + 2?(6))/3, (-9-2?(6))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 3, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 19\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*3*19))/(2*3) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*3*19))/(2*3)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(96))/6 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(96))/6", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 15x + 3 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(201))/4, (-15 -  ?(201))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 3\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*2*3))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*2*3))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(201))/4 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(201))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 15x + 12 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(33))/8, (-15 -  ?(33))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 12\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*4*12))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*4*12))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(33))/8 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(33))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n8x^2 + 14x + 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-7 + ?(17))/8, (-7 -  ?(17))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 8, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 4\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(14*14 - 4*8*4))/(2*8) or x \u003d (-14 - ?(14*14 - 4*8*4))/(2*8)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(68))/16 or x \u003d (-14 - ?(68))/16", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 15x + 2 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(193))/8, (-15 -  ?(193))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 2\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*4*2))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*4*2))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(193))/8 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(193))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 13x + 31 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-13 + 3?(5))/2, (-13-3?(5))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 13, c \u003d 31\nx \u003d (-13 + ?(13*13 - 4*1*31))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-13 - ?(13*13 - 4*1*31))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-13 + ?(45))/2 or x \u003d (-13 - ?(45))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 15x + 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(209))/8, (-15 -  ?(209))/8", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 1\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*4*1))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*4*1))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(209))/8 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(209))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 18x + 43 \u003d 0", "answer": "-9 + ?(38), -9 - ?(38)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 43\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*1*43))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*1*43))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(152))/2 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(152))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 16x + 41 \u003d 0", "answer": "-8 + ?(23), -8 - ?(23)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 41\nx \u003d (-16 + ?(16*16 - 4*1*41))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-16 - ?(16*16 - 4*1*41))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-16 + ?(92))/2 or x \u003d (-16 - ?(92))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 14x + 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "-7 + 4?(3), -7 - 4?(3)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 1\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(14*14 - 4*1*1))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-14 - ?(14*14 - 4*1*1))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(192))/2 or x \u003d (-14 - ?(192))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 19x + 43 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-19 + ?(17))/4, (-19 -  ?(17))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 43\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*2*43))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*2*43))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(17))/4 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(17))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 17x + 17 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-17 + ?(221))/2, (-17 -  ?(221))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 17\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(17*17 - 4*1*17))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-17 - ?(17*17 - 4*1*17))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(221))/2 or x \u003d (-17 - ?(221))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 20x + 19 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-5 + ?(6))/2, (-5 -  ?(6))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 19\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*4*19))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*4*19))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(96))/8 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(96))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n5x^2 + 19x + 7 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-19 + ?(221))/10, (-19 -  ?(221))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 5, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 7\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*5*7))/(2*5) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*5*7))/(2*5)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(221))/10 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(221))/10", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n5x^2 + 20x + 10 \u003d 0", "answer": "-2 + ?(2), -2 - ?(2)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 5, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 10\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*5*10))/(2*5) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*5*10))/(2*5)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(200))/10 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(200))/10", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n7x^2 + 18x + 3 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + 2?(15))/7, (-9-2?(15))/7", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 7, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 3\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*7*3))/(2*7) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*7*3))/(2*7)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(240))/14 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(240))/14", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 11x + 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-11 + ?(105))/2, (-11 -  ?(105))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 4\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(11*11 - 4*1*4))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-11 - ?(11*11 - 4*1*4))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(105))/2 or x \u003d (-11 - ?(105))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n5x^2 + 19x + 13 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-19 + ?(101))/10, (-19 -  ?(101))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 5, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 13\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*5*13))/(2*5) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*5*13))/(2*5)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(101))/10 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(101))/10", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 9x + 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(65))/2, (-9 -  ?(65))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 9, c \u003d 4\nx \u003d (-9 + ?(9*9 - 4*1*4))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-9 - ?(9*9 - 4*1*4))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-9 + ?(65))/2 or x \u003d (-9 - ?(65))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 20x + 20 \u003d 0", "answer": "-5 + ?(15), -5 - ?(15)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 20\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*2*20))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*2*20))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(240))/4 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(240))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n3x^2 + 6x + 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-3 + ?(6))/3, (-3 -  ?(6))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 3, b \u003d 6, c \u003d 1\nx \u003d (-6 + ?(6*6 - 4*3*1))/(2*3) or x \u003d (-6 - ?(6*6 - 4*3*1))/(2*3)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-6 + ?(24))/6 or x \u003d (-6 - ?(24))/6", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 18x + 18 \u003d 0", "answer": "-9 + 3?(7), -9 - 3?(7)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 18\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*1*18))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*1*18))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(252))/2 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(252))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n7x^2 + 15x + 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(113))/14, (-15 -  ?(113))/14", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 7, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 4\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*7*4))/(2*7) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*7*4))/(2*7)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(113))/14 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(113))/14", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 11x + 3 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-11 + ?(97))/4, (-11 -  ?(97))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 3\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(11*11 - 4*2*3))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-11 - ?(11*11 - 4*2*3))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(97))/4 or x \u003d (-11 - ?(97))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 14x + 7 \u003d 0", "answer": "-7 + ?(42), -7 - ?(42)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 7\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(14*14 - 4*1*7))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-14 - ?(14*14 - 4*1*7))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(168))/2 or x \u003d (-14 - ?(168))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n5x^2 + 10x + 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-5 + ?(5))/5, (-5 -  ?(5))/5", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 5, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 4\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(10*10 - 4*5*4))/(2*5) or x \u003d (-10 - ?(10*10 - 4*5*4))/(2*5)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(20))/10 or x \u003d (-10 - ?(20))/10", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 19x + 12 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-19 + ?(313))/2, (-19 -  ?(313))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 12\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*1*12))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*1*12))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(313))/2 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(313))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n5x^2 + 11x + 3 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-11 + ?(61))/10, (-11 -  ?(61))/10", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 5, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 3\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(11*11 - 4*5*3))/(2*5) or x \u003d (-11 - ?(11*11 - 4*5*3))/(2*5)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(61))/10 or x \u003d (-11 - ?(61))/10", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 12x + 11 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-6 + ?(14))/2, (-6 -  ?(14))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 12, c \u003d 11\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(12*12 - 4*2*11))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-12 - ?(12*12 - 4*2*11))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(56))/4 or x \u003d (-12 - ?(56))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 18x + 15 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(51))/2, (-9 -  ?(51))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 15\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*2*15))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*2*15))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(204))/4 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(204))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 7x + 5 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-7 + ?(29))/2, (-7 -  ?(29))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 7, c \u003d 5\nx \u003d (-7 + ?(7*7 - 4*1*5))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-7 - ?(7*7 - 4*1*5))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-7 + ?(29))/2 or x \u003d (-7 - ?(29))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 14x + 4 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-7 + ?(33))/4, (-7 -  ?(33))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 4\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(14*14 - 4*4*4))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-14 - ?(14*14 - 4*4*4))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(132))/8 or x \u003d (-14 - ?(132))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n3x^2 + 18x + 26 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(3))/3, (-9 -  ?(3))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 3, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 26\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*3*26))/(2*3) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*3*26))/(2*3)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(12))/6 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(12))/6", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 15x + 9 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + 3?(17))/4, (-15-3?(17))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 9\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*2*9))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*2*9))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(153))/4 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(153))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 19x + 2 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-19 + ?(345))/4, (-19 -  ?(345))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 2\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*2*2))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*2*2))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(345))/4 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(345))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n6x^2 + 19x + 7 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-19 + ?(193))/12, (-19 -  ?(193))/12", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 6, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 7\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*6*7))/(2*6) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*6*7))/(2*6)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(193))/12 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(193))/12", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 10x + 3 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-5 + ?(13))/4, (-5 -  ?(13))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 3\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(10*10 - 4*4*3))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-10 - ?(10*10 - 4*4*3))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(52))/8 or x \u003d (-10 - ?(52))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 11x + 2 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-11 + ?(113))/2, (-11 -  ?(113))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 11, c \u003d 2\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(11*11 - 4*1*2))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-11 - ?(11*11 - 4*1*2))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-11 + ?(113))/2 or x \u003d (-11 - ?(113))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 19x + 44 \u003d 0", "answer": "-4, -11/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 44\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*2*44))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*2*44))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(9))/4 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(9))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 19x + 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-19 + ?(313))/4, (-19 -  ?(313))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 6\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*2*6))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*2*6))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(313))/4 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(313))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n7x^2 + 18x + 2 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(67))/7, (-9 -  ?(67))/7", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 7, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 2\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*7*2))/(2*7) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*7*2))/(2*7)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(268))/14 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(268))/14", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 10x + 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-5 + ?(21))/4, (-5 -  ?(21))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 1\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(10*10 - 4*4*1))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-10 - ?(10*10 - 4*4*1))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(84))/8 or x \u003d (-10 - ?(84))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 16x + 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-4 + ?(10))/2, (-4 -  ?(10))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 16, c \u003d 6\nx \u003d (-16 + ?(16*16 - 4*4*6))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-16 - ?(16*16 - 4*4*6))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-16 + ?(160))/8 or x \u003d (-16 - ?(160))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 17x + 15 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-17 + ?(229))/2, (-17 -  ?(229))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 15\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(17*17 - 4*1*15))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-17 - ?(17*17 - 4*1*15))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(229))/2 or x \u003d (-17 - ?(229))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 18x + 43 \u003d 0", "answer": "-9 + ?(38), -9 - ?(38)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 43\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*1*43))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*1*43))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(152))/2 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(152))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 13x + 9 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-13 + ?(133))/2, (-13 -  ?(133))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 13, c \u003d 9\nx \u003d (-13 + ?(13*13 - 4*1*9))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-13 - ?(13*13 - 4*1*9))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-13 + ?(133))/2 or x \u003d (-13 - ?(133))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n3x^2 + 18x + 17 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + ?(30))/3, (-9 -  ?(30))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 3, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 17\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*3*17))/(2*3) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*3*17))/(2*3)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(120))/6 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(120))/6", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 19x + 20 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-19 + ?(201))/4, (-19 -  ?(201))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 19, c \u003d 20\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(19*19 - 4*2*20))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-19 - ?(19*19 - 4*2*20))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-19 + ?(201))/4 or x \u003d (-19 - ?(201))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 17x + 34 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-17 + ?(17))/4, (-17 -  ?(17))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 34\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(17*17 - 4*2*34))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-17 - ?(17*17 - 4*2*34))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(17))/4 or x \u003d (-17 - ?(17))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 20x + 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "-10 + ?(94), -10 - ?(94)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 6\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*1*6))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*1*6))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(376))/2 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(376))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 12x + 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "-6 + ?(30), -6 - ?(30)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 12, c \u003d 6\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(12*12 - 4*1*6))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-12 - ?(12*12 - 4*1*6))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(120))/2 or x \u003d (-12 - ?(120))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 10x + 5 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-5 + ?(5))/4, (-5 -  ?(5))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 10, c \u003d 5\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(10*10 - 4*4*5))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-10 - ?(10*10 - 4*4*5))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-10 + ?(20))/8 or x \u003d (-10 - ?(20))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 20x + 5 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-10 + 3?(10))/2, (-10-3?(10))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 5\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*2*5))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*2*5))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(360))/4 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(360))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n4x^2 + 20x + 22 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-5 + ?(3))/2, (-5 -  ?(3))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 4, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 22\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*4*22))/(2*4) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*4*22))/(2*4)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(48))/8 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(48))/8", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 20x + 29 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-10 + ?(42))/2, (-10 -  ?(42))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 29\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*2*29))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*2*29))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(168))/4 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(168))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n7x^2 + 17x + 1 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-17 + 3?(29))/14, (-17-3?(29))/14", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 7, b \u003d 17, c \u003d 1\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(17*17 - 4*7*1))/(2*7) or x \u003d (-17 - ?(17*17 - 4*7*1))/(2*7)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-17 + ?(261))/14 or x \u003d (-17 - ?(261))/14", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 15x + 40 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(65))/2, (-15 -  ?(65))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 40\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*1*40))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*1*40))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(65))/2 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(65))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n6x^2 + 12x + 2 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-3 + ?(6))/3, (-3 -  ?(6))/3", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 6, b \u003d 12, c \u003d 2\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(12*12 - 4*6*2))/(2*6) or x \u003d (-12 - ?(12*12 - 4*6*2))/(2*6)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(96))/12 or x \u003d (-12 - ?(96))/12", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 13x + 28 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-13 + ?(57))/2, (-13 -  ?(57))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 13, c \u003d 28\nx \u003d (-13 + ?(13*13 - 4*1*28))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-13 - ?(13*13 - 4*1*28))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-13 + ?(57))/2 or x \u003d (-13 - ?(57))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 12x + 10 \u003d 0", "answer": "-6 + ?(26), -6 - ?(26)", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 12, c \u003d 10\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(12*12 - 4*1*10))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-12 - ?(12*12 - 4*1*10))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-12 + ?(104))/2 or x \u003d (-12 - ?(104))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n5x^2 + 14x + 6 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-7 + ?(19))/5, (-7 -  ?(19))/5", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 5, b \u003d 14, c \u003d 6\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(14*14 - 4*5*6))/(2*5) or x \u003d (-14 - ?(14*14 - 4*5*6))/(2*5)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-14 + ?(76))/10 or x \u003d (-14 - ?(76))/10", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n2x^2 + 18x + 3 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-9 + 5?(3))/2, (-9-5?(3))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 2, b \u003d 18, c \u003d 3\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(18*18 - 4*2*3))/(2*2) or x \u003d (-18 - ?(18*18 - 4*2*3))/(2*2)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-18 + ?(300))/4 or x \u003d (-18 - ?(300))/4", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\n8x^2 + 20x + 9 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-5 + ?(7))/4, (-5 -  ?(7))/4", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 8, b \u003d 20, c \u003d 9\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(20*20 - 4*8*9))/(2*8) or x \u003d (-20 - ?(20*20 - 4*8*9))/(2*8)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-20 + ?(112))/16 or x \u003d (-20 - ?(112))/16", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Solve for x by using the quadratic formula:\nx^2 + 15x + 5 \u003d 0", "answer": "(-15 + ?(205))/2, (-15 -  ?(205))/2", "explanation": "Plug the coefficients into the quadratic formula:\na \u003d 1, b \u003d 15, c \u003d 5\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(15*15 - 4*1*5))/(2*1) or x \u003d (-15 - ?(15*15 - 4*1*5))/(2*1)\nSimplify\nx \u003d (-15 + ?(205))/2 or x \u003d (-15 - ?(205))/2", "prompt": "x \u003d"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 28", "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -28, -1 \u0026 28, 2 \u0026 -14, -2 \u0026 14, 4 \u0026 -7, -4 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are -4 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x + 4", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 4, -1 \u0026 -4, 2 \u0026 2, -2 \u0026 -2\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 4 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 36", "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -36, -1 \u0026 36, 2 \u0026 -18, -2 \u0026 18, 3 \u0026 -12, -3 \u0026 12, 4 \u0026 -9, -4 \u0026 9, 6 \u0026 -6, -6 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are -6 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x - 27", "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -27, -1 \u0026 27, 3 \u0026 -9, -3 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 9 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 2x - 63", "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -63, -1 \u0026 63, 3 \u0026 -21, -3 \u0026 21, 7 \u0026 -9, -7 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 2 are -7 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 13x + 42", "answer": "(x - 7)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 42, -1 \u0026 -42, 2 \u0026 21, -2 \u0026 -21, 3 \u0026 14, -3 \u0026 -14, 6 \u0026 7, -6 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -13 are -7 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 54", "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -54, -1 \u0026 54, 2 \u0026 -27, -2 \u0026 27, 3 \u0026 -18, -3 \u0026 18, 6 \u0026 -9, -6 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 9 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 14x + 48", "answer": "(x + 8)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 48, -1 \u0026 -48, 2 \u0026 24, -2 \u0026 -24, 3 \u0026 16, -3 \u0026 -16, 4 \u0026 12, -4 \u0026 -12, 6 \u0026 8, -6 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal 14 are 8 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 2x - 15", "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -15, -1 \u0026 15, 3 \u0026 -5, -3 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal 2 are -3 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 9x + 14", "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 14, -1 \u0026 -14, 2 \u0026 7, -2 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 9 are 7 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x - 32", "answer": "(x + 8)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -32, -1 \u0026 32, 2 \u0026 -16, -2 \u0026 16, 4 \u0026 -8, -4 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are 8 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x - 5", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -5, -1 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are 1 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 4", "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -4, -1 \u0026 4, 2 \u0026 -2, -2 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 4 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 11x + 18", "answer": "(x - 9)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 18, -1 \u0026 -18, 2 \u0026 9, -2 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 6, -3 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal -11 are -9 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 7x - 8", "answer": "(x + 8)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal 7 are 8 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 15x + 54", "answer": "(x + 9)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 54, -1 \u0026 -54, 2 \u0026 27, -2 \u0026 -27, 3 \u0026 18, -3 \u0026 -18, 6 \u0026 9, -6 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal 15 are 9 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 13x + 42", "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 42, -1 \u0026 -42, 2 \u0026 21, -2 \u0026 -21, 3 \u0026 14, -3 \u0026 -14, 6 \u0026 7, -6 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 13 are 7 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16x + 64", "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 64, -1 \u0026 -64, 2 \u0026 32, -2 \u0026 -32, 4 \u0026 16, -4 \u0026 -16, 8 \u0026 8, -8 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal -16 are -8 and -8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x + 8", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 8, -1 \u0026 -8, 2 \u0026 4, -2 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 4 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 13x + 36", "answer": "(x - 9)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 36, -1 \u0026 -36, 2 \u0026 18, -2 \u0026 -18, 3 \u0026 12, -3 \u0026 -12, 4 \u0026 9, -4 \u0026 -9, 6 \u0026 6, -6 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal -13 are -9 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x + 3", "answer": "(x + 1)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 3, -1 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are 1 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 36", "answer": "(x + 6)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -36, -1 \u0026 36, 2 \u0026 -18, -2 \u0026 18, 3 \u0026 -12, -3 \u0026 12, 4 \u0026 -9, -4 \u0026 9, 6 \u0026 -6, -6 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are 6 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9x + 20", "answer": "(x - 5)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 20, -1 \u0026 -20, 2 \u0026 10, -2 \u0026 -10, 4 \u0026 5, -4 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal -9 are -5 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 1", "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -1, -1 \u0026 1\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are -1 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 40", "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -40, -1 \u0026 40, 2 \u0026 -20, -2 \u0026 20, 4 \u0026 -10, -4 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -8, -5 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are -5 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 11x + 28", "answer": "(x - 4)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 28, -1 \u0026 -28, 2 \u0026 14, -2 \u0026 -14, 4 \u0026 7, -4 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -11 are -4 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x - 6", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -6, -1 \u0026 6, 2 \u0026 -3, -2 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are 1 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 14x + 45", "answer": "(x - 5)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 45, -1 \u0026 -45, 3 \u0026 15, -3 \u0026 -15, 5 \u0026 9, -5 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -14 are -5 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 7x + 10", "answer": "(x - 2)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 10, -1 \u0026 -10, 2 \u0026 5, -2 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal -7 are -2 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 24", "answer": "(x + 6)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 24, -1 \u0026 -24, 2 \u0026 12, -2 \u0026 -12, 3 \u0026 8, -3 \u0026 -8, 4 \u0026 6, -4 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 6 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x + 6", "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are -3 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 14x + 45", "answer": "(x - 5)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 45, -1 \u0026 -45, 3 \u0026 15, -3 \u0026 -15, 5 \u0026 9, -5 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -14 are -5 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x - 7", "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -7, -1 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are -1 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 35", "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -35, -1 \u0026 35, 5 \u0026 -7, -5 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are -7 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 24", "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -24, -1 \u0026 24, 2 \u0026 -12, -2 \u0026 12, 3 \u0026 -8, -3 \u0026 8, 4 \u0026 -6, -4 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are -6 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 15x + 56", "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 56, -1 \u0026 -56, 2 \u0026 28, -2 \u0026 -28, 4 \u0026 14, -4 \u0026 -14, 7 \u0026 8, -7 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal 15 are 7 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 15x + 54", "answer": "(x - 9)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 54, -1 \u0026 -54, 2 \u0026 27, -2 \u0026 -27, 3 \u0026 18, -3 \u0026 -18, 6 \u0026 9, -6 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -15 are -9 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 6x + 8", "answer": "(x - 4)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 8, -1 \u0026 -8, 2 \u0026 4, -2 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal -6 are -4 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x - 27", "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -27, -1 \u0026 27, 3 \u0026 -9, -3 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are -3 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 7x + 10", "answer": "(x + 2)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 10, -1 \u0026 -10, 2 \u0026 5, -2 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal 7 are 2 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 3x - 40", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -40, -1 \u0026 40, 2 \u0026 -20, -2 \u0026 20, 4 \u0026 -10, -4 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -8, -5 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal -3 are -8 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x - 14", "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -14, -1 \u0026 14, 2 \u0026 -7, -2 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are -7 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x - 21", "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -21, -1 \u0026 21, 3 \u0026 -7, -3 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are -3 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x - 32", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -32, -1 \u0026 32, 2 \u0026 -16, -2 \u0026 16, 4 \u0026 -8, -4 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are -8 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 1", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -1, -1 \u0026 1\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are 1 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 14x + 45", "answer": "(x - 9)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 45, -1 \u0026 -45, 3 \u0026 15, -3 \u0026 -15, 5 \u0026 9, -5 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -14 are -9 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 32", "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 32, -1 \u0026 -32, 2 \u0026 16, -2 \u0026 -16, 4 \u0026 8, -4 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -8 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 30", "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -30, -1 \u0026 30, 2 \u0026 -15, -2 \u0026 15, 3 \u0026 -10, -3 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -6, -5 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are -5 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x + 3", "answer": "(x + 1)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 3, -1 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are 1 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 2", "answer": "(x - 2)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -2, -1 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -2 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 11x + 30", "answer": "(x + 6)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 30, -1 \u0026 -30, 2 \u0026 15, -2 \u0026 -15, 3 \u0026 10, -3 \u0026 -10, 5 \u0026 6, -5 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal 11 are 6 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 11x + 18", "answer": "(x + 9)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 18, -1 \u0026 -18, 2 \u0026 9, -2 \u0026 -9, 3 \u0026 6, -3 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal 11 are 9 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 3", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -3, -1 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are 1 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 72", "answer": "(x + 8)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -72, -1 \u0026 72, 2 \u0026 -36, -2 \u0026 36, 3 \u0026 -24, -3 \u0026 24, 4 \u0026 -18, -4 \u0026 18, 6 \u0026 -12, -6 \u0026 12, 8 \u0026 -9, -8 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are 8 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x + 6", "answer": "(x + 2)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 2 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 20", "answer": "(x + 5)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -20, -1 \u0026 20, 2 \u0026 -10, -2 \u0026 10, 4 \u0026 -5, -4 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are 5 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 42", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -42, -1 \u0026 42, 2 \u0026 -21, -2 \u0026 21, 3 \u0026 -14, -3 \u0026 14, 6 \u0026 -7, -6 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are 7 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 7x - 18", "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -18, -1 \u0026 18, 2 \u0026 -9, -2 \u0026 9, 3 \u0026 -6, -3 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal -7 are 2 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 13x + 36", "answer": "(x - 4)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 36, -1 \u0026 -36, 2 \u0026 18, -2 \u0026 -18, 3 \u0026 12, -3 \u0026 -12, 4 \u0026 9, -4 \u0026 -9, 6 \u0026 6, -6 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal -13 are -4 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 49", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -49, -1 \u0026 49, 7 \u0026 -7, -7 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are 7 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 20", "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -20, -1 \u0026 20, 2 \u0026 -10, -2 \u0026 10, 4 \u0026 -5, -4 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -5 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 14x + 48", "answer": "(x - 6)(x - 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 48, -1 \u0026 -48, 2 \u0026 24, -2 \u0026 -24, 3 \u0026 16, -3 \u0026 -16, 4 \u0026 12, -4 \u0026 -12, 6 \u0026 8, -6 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal -14 are -6 and -8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 2x - 35", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -35, -1 \u0026 35, 5 \u0026 -7, -5 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 2 are 7 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 28", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -28, -1 \u0026 28, 2 \u0026 -14, -2 \u0026 14, 4 \u0026 -7, -4 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 7 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 40", "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -40, -1 \u0026 40, 2 \u0026 -20, -2 \u0026 20, 4 \u0026 -10, -4 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -8, -5 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are -5 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + x - 6", "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -6, -1 \u0026 6, 2 \u0026 -3, -2 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal 1 are 3 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 3x - 4", "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -4, -1 \u0026 4, 2 \u0026 -2, -2 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal -3 are -4 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 18x + 81", "answer": "(x + 9)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 81, -1 \u0026 -81, 3 \u0026 27, -3 \u0026 -27, 9 \u0026 9, -9 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal 18 are 9 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 16x + 63", "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 63, -1 \u0026 -63, 3 \u0026 21, -3 \u0026 -21, 7 \u0026 9, -7 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal 16 are 7 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9", "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -9, -1 \u0026 9, 3 \u0026 -3, -3 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are -3 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 8x + 7", "answer": "(x - 7)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 7, -1 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -8 are -7 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x - 36", "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -36, -1 \u0026 36, 2 \u0026 -18, -2 \u0026 18, 3 \u0026 -12, -3 \u0026 12, 4 \u0026 -9, -4 \u0026 9, 6 \u0026 -6, -6 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are -4 and 9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 2", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -2, -1 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are 1 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 1", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -1, -1 \u0026 1\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are 1 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 11x + 24", "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 24, -1 \u0026 -24, 2 \u0026 12, -2 \u0026 -12, 3 \u0026 8, -3 \u0026 -8, 4 \u0026 6, -4 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal -11 are -8 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 35", "answer": "(x - 7)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 35, -1 \u0026 -35, 5 \u0026 7, -5 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -7 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x - 5", "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -5, -1 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are -1 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 7x + 6", "answer": "(x + 6)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 7 are 6 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 2x - 8", "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal 2 are 4 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 6x - 16", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -16, -1 \u0026 16, 2 \u0026 -8, -2 \u0026 8, 4 \u0026 -4, -4 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal -6 are -8 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 14x + 48", "answer": "(x + 6)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 48, -1 \u0026 -48, 2 \u0026 24, -2 \u0026 -24, 3 \u0026 16, -3 \u0026 -16, 4 \u0026 12, -4 \u0026 -12, 6 \u0026 8, -6 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal 14 are 6 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 8", "answer": "(x + 2)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are 2 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 14x + 45", "answer": "(x - 5)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 45, -1 \u0026 -45, 3 \u0026 15, -3 \u0026 -15, 5 \u0026 9, -5 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -14 are -5 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9", "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -9, -1 \u0026 9, 3 \u0026 -3, -3 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are -3 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x + 4", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 4, -1 \u0026 -4, 2 \u0026 2, -2 \u0026 -2\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 4 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x - 6", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -6, -1 \u0026 6, 2 \u0026 -3, -2 \u0026 3\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are 1 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 7x + 10", "answer": "(x + 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 10, -1 \u0026 -10, 2 \u0026 5, -2 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal 7 are 5 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x + 6", "answer": "(x - 2)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are -2 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 40", "answer": "(x + 8)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -40, -1 \u0026 40, 2 \u0026 -20, -2 \u0026 20, 4 \u0026 -10, -4 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -8, -5 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 8 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x + 3", "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 3, -1 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are -3 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x - 5", "answer": "(x - 5)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -5, -1 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are -5 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 8x + 7", "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 7, -1 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 8 are 7 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9x + 14", "answer": "(x - 7)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 14, -1 \u0026 -14, 2 \u0026 7, -2 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -9 are -7 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 48", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -48, -1 \u0026 48, 2 \u0026 -24, -2 \u0026 24, 3 \u0026 -16, -3 \u0026 16, 4 \u0026 -12, -4 \u0026 12, 6 \u0026 -8, -6 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are -8 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 54", "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -54, -1 \u0026 54, 2 \u0026 -27, -2 \u0026 27, 3 \u0026 -18, -3 \u0026 18, 6 \u0026 -9, -6 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 9 and -6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 7x - 8", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal -7 are 1 and -8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x - 32", "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -32, -1 \u0026 32, 2 \u0026 -16, -2 \u0026 16, 4 \u0026 -8, -4 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are -4 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x - 36", "answer": "(x + 9)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -36, -1 \u0026 36, 2 \u0026 -18, -2 \u0026 18, 3 \u0026 -12, -3 \u0026 12, 4 \u0026 -9, -4 \u0026 9, 6 \u0026 -6, -6 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 9 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 8x + 12", "answer": "(x - 6)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 12, -1 \u0026 -12, 2 \u0026 6, -2 \u0026 -6, 3 \u0026 4, -3 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal -8 are -6 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x - 14", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -14, -1 \u0026 14, 2 \u0026 -7, -2 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 7 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 7x + 12", "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 12, -1 \u0026 -12, 2 \u0026 6, -2 \u0026 -6, 3 \u0026 4, -3 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 7 are 3 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 2x - 63", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -63, -1 \u0026 63, 3 \u0026 -21, -3 \u0026 21, 7 \u0026 -9, -7 \u0026 9\nThe two factors that add to equal -2 are 7 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 9x + 8", "answer": "(x + 1)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 8, -1 \u0026 -8, 2 \u0026 4, -2 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 9 are 1 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 35", "answer": "(x - 7)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 35, -1 \u0026 -35, 5 \u0026 7, -5 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -7 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 49", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -49, -1 \u0026 49, 7 \u0026 -7, -7 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are 7 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 7x - 8", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -8, -1 \u0026 8, 2 \u0026 -4, -2 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal -7 are -8 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 32", "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 32, -1 \u0026 -32, 2 \u0026 16, -2 \u0026 -16, 4 \u0026 8, -4 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -8 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x + 6", "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 3 and 2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 17x + 72", "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 72, -1 \u0026 -72, 2 \u0026 36, -2 \u0026 -36, 3 \u0026 24, -3 \u0026 -24, 4 \u0026 18, -4 \u0026 -18, 6 \u0026 12, -6 \u0026 -12, 8 \u0026 9, -8 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -17 are -8 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 5x + 4", "answer": "(x - 4)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 4, -1 \u0026 -4, 2 \u0026 2, -2 \u0026 -2\nThe two factors that add to equal -5 are -4 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 27", "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 27, -1 \u0026 -27, 3 \u0026 9, -3 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -3 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 28", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -28, -1 \u0026 28, 2 \u0026 -14, -2 \u0026 14, 4 \u0026 -7, -4 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 7 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 24", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 24, -1 \u0026 -24, 2 \u0026 12, -2 \u0026 -12, 3 \u0026 8, -3 \u0026 -8, 4 \u0026 6, -4 \u0026 -6\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 4 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 2x - 35", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -35, -1 \u0026 35, 5 \u0026 -7, -5 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 2 are 7 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 8x + 15", "answer": "(x - 5)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 15, -1 \u0026 -15, 3 \u0026 5, -3 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal -8 are -5 and -3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 27", "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 27, -1 \u0026 -27, 3 \u0026 9, -3 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -3 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 32", "answer": "(x - 4)(x - 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 32, -1 \u0026 -32, 2 \u0026 16, -2 \u0026 -16, 4 \u0026 8, -4 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -4 and -8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 16x + 63", "answer": "(x + 9)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 63, -1 \u0026 -63, 3 \u0026 21, -3 \u0026 -21, 7 \u0026 9, -7 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal 16 are 9 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 4", "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -4, -1 \u0026 4, 2 \u0026 -2, -2 \u0026 2\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are 4 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 12x + 35", "answer": "(x - 5)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 35, -1 \u0026 -35, 5 \u0026 7, -5 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -12 are -5 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 13x + 42", "answer": "(x - 6)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 42, -1 \u0026 -42, 2 \u0026 21, -2 \u0026 -21, 3 \u0026 14, -3 \u0026 -14, 6 \u0026 7, -6 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -13 are -6 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x - 12", "answer": "(x - 2)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -12, -1 \u0026 12, 2 \u0026 -6, -2 \u0026 6, 3 \u0026 -4, -3 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are -2 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 5x - 14", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -14, -1 \u0026 14, 2 \u0026 -7, -2 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 5 are 7 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 7x + 6", "answer": "(x + 6)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 6, -1 \u0026 -6, 2 \u0026 3, -2 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 7 are 6 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - x - 30", "answer": "(x - 6)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -30, -1 \u0026 30, 2 \u0026 -15, -2 \u0026 15, 3 \u0026 -10, -3 \u0026 10, 5 \u0026 -6, -5 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal -1 are -6 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 10x + 21", "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 21, -1 \u0026 -21, 3 \u0026 7, -3 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -10 are -3 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 10x + 21", "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 21, -1 \u0026 -21, 3 \u0026 7, -3 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 10 are 7 and 3\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9x + 14", "answer": "(x - 2)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 14, -1 \u0026 -14, 2 \u0026 7, -2 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal -9 are -2 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 3x - 28", "answer": "(x - 7)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -28, -1 \u0026 28, 2 \u0026 -14, -2 \u0026 14, 4 \u0026 -7, -4 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -3 are -7 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 6x + 8", "answer": "(x - 4)(x - 2)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 8, -1 \u0026 -8, 2 \u0026 4, -2 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal -6 are -4 and -2\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 8x + 16", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 16, -1 \u0026 -16, 2 \u0026 8, -2 \u0026 -8, 4 \u0026 4, -4 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 8 are 4 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x - 7", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -7, -1 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 7 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9x + 20", "answer": "(x - 4)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 20, -1 \u0026 -20, 2 \u0026 10, -2 \u0026 -10, 4 \u0026 5, -4 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal -9 are -4 and -5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 17x + 72", "answer": "(x - 8)(x - 9)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 72, -1 \u0026 -72, 2 \u0026 36, -2 \u0026 -36, 3 \u0026 24, -3 \u0026 -24, 4 \u0026 18, -4 \u0026 -18, 6 \u0026 12, -6 \u0026 -12, 8 \u0026 9, -8 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal -17 are -8 and -9\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 64", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -64, -1 \u0026 64, 2 \u0026 -32, -2 \u0026 32, 4 \u0026 -16, -4 \u0026 16, 8 \u0026 -8, -8 \u0026 8\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are -8 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 12x + 32", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 32, -1 \u0026 -32, 2 \u0026 16, -2 \u0026 -16, 4 \u0026 8, -4 \u0026 -8\nThe two factors that add to equal 12 are 4 and 8\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 11x + 28", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 28, -1 \u0026 -28, 2 \u0026 14, -2 \u0026 -14, 4 \u0026 7, -4 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 11 are 4 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x + 3", "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 3, -1 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are 3 and 1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 8x + 12", "answer": "(x + 2)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 12, -1 \u0026 -12, 2 \u0026 6, -2 \u0026 -6, 3 \u0026 4, -3 \u0026 -4\nThe two factors that add to equal 8 are 2 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 3x - 18", "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -18, -1 \u0026 18, 2 \u0026 -9, -2 \u0026 9, 3 \u0026 -6, -3 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal 3 are -3 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 4x + 3", "answer": "(x - 3)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 3, -1 \u0026 -3\nThe two factors that add to equal -4 are -3 and -1\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 2x - 24", "answer": "(x - 4)(x + 6)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -24, -1 \u0026 24, 2 \u0026 -12, -2 \u0026 12, 3 \u0026 -8, -3 \u0026 8, 4 \u0026 -6, -4 \u0026 6\nThe two factors that add to equal 2 are -4 and 6\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 16x + 63", "answer": "(x + 9)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 63, -1 \u0026 -63, 3 \u0026 21, -3 \u0026 -21, 7 \u0026 9, -7 \u0026 -9\nThe two factors that add to equal 16 are 9 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 11x + 28", "answer": "(x + 7)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 28, -1 \u0026 -28, 2 \u0026 14, -2 \u0026 -14, 4 \u0026 7, -4 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 11 are 7 and 4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -16, -1 \u0026 16, 2 \u0026 -8, -2 \u0026 8, 4 \u0026 -4, -4 \u0026 4\nThe two factors that add to equal 0 are 4 and -4\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 11x + 28", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 28, -1 \u0026 -28, 2 \u0026 14, -2 \u0026 -14, 4 \u0026 7, -4 \u0026 -7\nThe two factors that add to equal 11 are 4 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 6x + 5", "answer": "(x + 1)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 5, -1 \u0026 -5\nThe two factors that add to equal 6 are 1 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x - 5", "answer": "(x - 1)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -5, -1 \u0026 5\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are -1 and 5\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 + 4x - 21", "answer": "(x - 3)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -21, -1 \u0026 21, 3 \u0026 -7, -3 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal 4 are -3 and 7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 3x - 28", "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Find pairs of factors that multiply to equal the last term.\n1 \u0026 -28, -1 \u0026 28, 2 \u0026 -14, -2 \u0026 14, 4 \u0026 -7, -4 \u0026 7\nThe two factors that add to equal -3 are 4 and -7\nWrite the equation as a product of two binomials.", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 64", "answer": "(x - 4)(x^2 + 4x + 16)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 4^3", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 16", "answer": "(x + 4)(x - 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 25", "answer": "(x + 5)(x - 5)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 5^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 5^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 27", "answer": "(x - 3)(x^2 + 3x + 9)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 3^3", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 125", "answer": "(x + 5)(x^2 - 5x + 25)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 5^3", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n36x^2 - 9", "answer": "(6x - 3)(6x + 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (6x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (6x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 100", "answer": "(x - 10)(x + 10)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 10^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 10^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n81x^2 - 36", "answer": "(9x + 6)(9x - 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (9x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (9x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n25x^2 - 1", "answer": "(5x + 1)(5x - 1)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (5x)^2 - 1^2\na \u003d (5x)^2, b \u003d 1^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 49", "answer": "(x + 7)(x - 7)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 7^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 7^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 512", "answer": "(x - 8)(x^2 + 8x + 64)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 8^3", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 64", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n81x^2 - 16", "answer": "(9x + 4)(9x - 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (9x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (9x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 64", "answer": "(x - 8)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 8^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 8^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 36", "answer": "(x + 6)(x - 6)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 6^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 6^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 - 216", "answer": "(x - 6)(x^2 + 6x + 36)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is negative.\nFactor the equation using the difference of cubes formula.\n(a - b)(a^2 + ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 - 6^3", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 9", "answer": "(x + 3)(x - 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 125", "answer": "(x + 5)(x^2 - 5x + 25)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 5^3", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n36x^2 - 9", "answer": "(6x - 3)(6x + 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (6x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (6x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n81x^2 - 9", "answer": "(9x - 3)(9x + 3)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (9x)^2 - 3^2\na \u003d (9x)^2, b \u003d 3^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n36x^2 - 49", "answer": "(6x + 7)(6x - 7)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (6x)^2 - 7^2\na \u003d (6x)^2, b \u003d 7^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^3 + 343", "answer": "(x + 7)(x^2 - 7x + 49)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect perfect cubes and the constant is positive.\nFactor the equation using the sum of cubes formula.\n(a + b)(a^2 - ab + b^2) \u003d x^3 + 7^3", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n25x^2 - 100", "answer": "(5x + 10)(5x - 10)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (5x)^2 - 10^2\na \u003d (5x)^2, b \u003d 10^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\n64x^2 - 16", "answer": "(8x + 4)(8x - 4)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (8x)^2 - 4^2\na \u003d (8x)^2, b \u003d 4^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Factor:\nx^2 - 1", "answer": "(x + 1)(x - 1)", "explanation": "Both terms are perfect squares and the constant is negative\nFactor the equation using the difference of squares formula.\n(a + b)(a - b) \u003d (x)^2 - 1^2\na \u003d (x)^2, b \u003d 1^2", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-11x^2 + 13x + 14", "answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-11x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n10x^6 + 15x^4 - 13x^3 + 7x^2 + 12x + 15", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n10x^6\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-9x + 12", "answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-9x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x + 6", "answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^3y^3 - 3x^2y^3 - 3xy^3 + 9", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x^3y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n4x^5y^3 - 8x^4y^3 + 13x^3y^3 + x^2y^3 - 5xy^3 + 9", "answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n4x^5y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-5x^2y - 8xy - 2", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-5x^2y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-2x^2 - 3x - 12", "answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-2x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-2x^5y^5 + x^4y^3 + 3x^3y^3 - 12x", "answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-2x^5y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n11x^2y^3 - 1", "answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n11x^2y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-5x^6y^4 - 2x^5y^5 + 10x^4y^4 + 11x^3y^5 - 4x^2y^4 + 5xy^5 + 7", "answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-5x^6y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^2y^2 + 3xy^2 + 3", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n14x^3y^3 + 2x^2y^3 - 12xy^3 + 4", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n14x^3y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-6x^2 + 7x - 8", "answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-6x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-x^2 + 14x + 5", "answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-x^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-6x^3 + 14x^2 + 15x + 15", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-6x^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-10x^6y^4 + 13x^5y^4 + 3x^4y^6 + 6x^2y^4 - 2xy^6 - 13", "answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-10x^6y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-6x^3 + x^2 + 9x - 6", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-6x^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n3x^4 - 2x^3 + x^2 + x - 13", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n3x^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-4x^3y - 4x^2y - 11xy + 12", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-4x^3y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n4x^4y + 6x^3y^2 + 5x^2y^4 + 4xy^4 - 12", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n6x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-5x^5y^3 + 10x^4y^3 - 6x^3y^3 - 6x^2y^3 + 13xy^3 - 10", "answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-5x^5y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n7x^6y^5 + 3x^5y^5 + 7x^4y^5 - 10x^2y^5 + 10xy^5 - 3", "answer": "11", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n7x^6y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n2x^7y^2 - x^5y^2 - 3x^4y^2 + 15x^3y^2 + 13x^2y^2 - 10xy^2 + 2", "answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n2x^7y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n3x^2y^2 - 11xy^2 - 13", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n3x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-10x^3 + 13x^2 + 11x + 10", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-10x^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n5x^3y^3 - 11x^2y^3 - 4xy^3 + 7", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n5x^3y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-7x^2y^2 + 1", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-7x^2y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-11x^5y^4 + 6x^4y^5 + 7x^3y^5 + 12x^2y^4 + 15", "answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-11x^5y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-2xy - 12", "answer": "2", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-2xy\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n9x + 6", "answer": "1", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n9x\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-13x^4 - 5x^3 + 15x^2 + 11x + 5", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-13x^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n14x^7y^3 - 11x^6y - 4x^5y^3 + 7x^3y^3 + 8x^2y + 7xy^3 - 6", "answer": "10", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n14x^7y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n8x^3y^3 + 7x^2y^3 - 7xy^3 - 6", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n8x^3y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-5x^6y^5 + 14x^5y^5 - 9x^4y^5 - 2x^3y^5 - 4x^2y^5 + 14xy^5 - 12", "answer": "11", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-5x^6y^5\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n9x^4y^4 + 3x^3y^3 + 5x^2y^4 + 4xy^3 + 7", "answer": "8", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n9x^4y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-9x^5y + 5x^4y - 2x^3y - x^2y - 10xy + 4", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-9x^5y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-3x^5y^4 - 13x^4y^2 - 7x^3y^5 - 8x^2y^2 + 10xy^2 + 8", "answer": "9", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-3x^5y^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-12x^3y^2 + 7x^2y^2 - 7xy^2 - 3", "answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-12x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-7x^4 - 10x^2 + 6x - 8", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-7x^4\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-10x^7y^6 + x^6y + 5x^5y^6 - 3x^4y + 12x^3y^6 - 13x^2y^6 - 4xy^5 - 11", "answer": "13", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-10x^7y^6\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-11x^3y^2 + 5x^2y^2 - 8x", "answer": "5", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-11x^3y^2\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n9x^3y^3 + 3x^2y^3 - 6xy^3 + 10", "answer": "6", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n9x^3y^3\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n10x^2y - 8xy + 13", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n10x^2y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Find the degree of the following polynomial:\n-5x^2y + 5xy - 2", "answer": "3", "explanation": "Finding the term with the greatest sum of exponents\n-5x^2y\nThe sum of the exponents is the degree of the polynomial", "prompt": ""}
]}